http://www.airwalk.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyPublished: April 1, 2016This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies only to the website owned, operated and maintained by ABG Collective, LLC (referred to herein as "we" or "us") where this Privacy Policy is posted (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information we collect both online and offline. BY USING THE SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE. A. Information CollectedWe collect the information you provide to us actively, and also collect information automatically from the devices that interact with our Site, as explained below. (1) Information You Actively Provide"We collect registration details and personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, age, gender, payment details, purchase history, or company name, that you actively provide to us when you register, communicate, or transact business with our Site. We receive and store the information that you enter on our Site or give to us in any other way. The above list provides an example of the personally identifiable information that may be collected on the Site. If you do not want us to collect your personally identifiable information, please do not provide it to us. (2) Information Collected From or About the Devices that Interact with our SiteWe receive and store information from and about the devices (such computers, smartphones) that interact with our device, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; your login credentials; and computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform. We use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to measure and collect session information, including page response times, and to measure and understand visitor behaviors on the site. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for reasons of security and site integrity. B. Use of Information Collected Via the Site(1) We use the information that you actively provideTo deliver services, such as educational programs, information, newsletters or software you request or purchase;To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from us, or other third parties, or to forward promotional materials;To complete a transaction or service requested by you;To fulfill the terms of a promotion;To customize your experience with us, to modify our products and services and to ensure the Site are relevant to your needs;To help us create and publish content most relevant to you;To notify you about a material change to this Privacy Policy or the Visitor Agreement, if necessary;To allow you access to limited-entry areas of the Site; To contact you in response to sign up forms such as Contact Us or Order Inquiry;For security purposes (e.g., we may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites); andAs otherwise permitted under applicable law.C. Sharing and Disclosure of InformationWe may share or disclose the information you provide, including name and contact details in the following instances:(i) To fulfill a service to you. For example, if you choose to watch an educational program on the Site, we may share your personally identifiable information in order to provide the program to you. In addition, if you email us a question, we may use your email address to process your request and respond to your question. Also, if you are entering a sweepstakes or contest, we may use your personally identifiable information in order to fulfill the terms of that promotion. This means that we may share the information for prize fulfillment purposes or mail carriers. We also may share your information with the co-sponsor of that promotion. (ii) To affiliates, strategic partners, agents, third party marketers or other unaffiliated parties who are offering products or services that we believe may be of interest to you or who require your personally identifiable information for research, administrative and/or internal business purposes. These parties may use your personally identifiable information to contact you with an offer or advertisement related to a product or service, or they may use such information for their own research, administration or business purposes. If you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information in this manner, please do not provide us with this information. (iii) To unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents or independent contractors who help us maintain our Site and provide other administrative services to us (including, but not limited to, order processing and fulfillment, providing customer service, maintaining and analyzing data, sending customer communications on our behalf, and entry collection, winner selection and prize fulfillment for contests, sweepstakes and other promotions). We seek to ensure that these unaffiliated third parties will not use the personally identifiable information for any other purpose than to provide the administrative services for which they are responsible. Because such unaffiliated third-party service providers that help us administer our Site will have access to users' personally identifiable information, if you do not wish for our unaffiliated third-party service providers to have access to your information, please do not register or submit any personally identifiable information to us. (iv) To complete your purchase. If you choose to make a purchase on the Site, we may collect from you your credit card number, billing address and other information related to such purchase, and we may use such collected information in order to fulfill your purchase. We may also provide such information, or other personally identifiable information provided by you, to unaffiliated third parties as necessary to complete your purchase (for example, to process your credit card). (v) To comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us, protect and defend our rights or property or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our end users. (vi) As part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited to, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets.(vii) To track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.(viii) To protect against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the information collected from these Site. In the course of such verification, we may receive personally identifiable information about you from such services. In particular, if you use a credit card or debit card to purchase services with us, we may use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to us, and that the card has not been reported as lost or stolen. Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not otherwise use, share or otherwise disclose your name and contact or payment details to any third parties.D. Online Tracking / Third Party AdvertisingWe use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies for analytics and advertising purposes. When you interact with our Site, interest-based ads may be displayed to you based upon information such as purchasing or browsing behaviors on our Site. These tracking technologies enable us to identify the ads you see, whether you click on them, and other actions you take on our Site, so that we can tailor advertising, including for example avoiding repetition of ad content. We do not use personal information, such as name or contact details, to tailor advertising. We may use advertisers, third party ad networks, and other advertising companies, to serve advertisements on the Site. Please be advised that such advertising companies may gather information about your visit to the Site or other sites (such as through cookies, web beacons and other technologies) to enable such advertising companies to market products or services to you, to monitor which ads have been served to your browser and which webpages you were viewing when such ads were delivered. These advertisers may read and place cookies on our Site, but they do not have access to personal information such as name or contact details. Our Site, whether accessed on a computer or a mobile device, is not at this time configured to read or respond to “do not track” settings or signals in your browser headings, which vary by browser provider. In lieu of a browser-based opt-out solution, users can utilize the Digital Advertising Alliance and other approved methods for placement of “opt-out” cookies. Our site and those of our third party advertisers or other vendors are configured to read and honor these opt-out cookies, so long as they are present on your computer. (If you delete all cookies, you will need to reset your opt-out cookies.) Specific instructions on how to do so follow. However, please be aware that we do not control these opt-out processes. E. ChildrenThe features, programs, promotions and other aspects of this Site requiring personally identifiable information are not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of thirteen (13) and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at legaldept@authenticbrandsgroup.com. A parent or guardian of a child under the age of thirteen (13) may review and request deletion of such child’s personally identifiable information as well as prohibit the use thereof. F. International Transfer of InformationIf you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, we may transfer that information to its affiliates and subsidiaries or to other third parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personally identifiable information you consent to: The use of your personally identifiable information for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; andThe transfer of your personally identifiable information to the United States as indicated above.G. Opt-OutWe communicate with users who subscribe to our services on a regular basis via email. For example, we may use your email address to confirm your request, to send you notice of payments, to send you information about changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures as required by law. Generally, users cannot opt-out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional. However, we provide you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive other types of communication from us, such as emails or updates from us regarding new services and products offered on this Site or if you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information with third parties. The opt-out choice may be exercised by ticking or un-ticking the appropriate box if such checkbox is available at the points where personally identifiable information is collected or by contacting us. We will process your unsubscribe as soon as possible, but please be aware that in some circumstances you may receive a few more messages until the unsubscribe is processed. You also may opt-out of receiving such emails by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link within the text of the email. H. Forums, Chat Rooms, and Other Public Posting AreasPlease note that any information you include in a message you post to any chat room, forum or other public posting area is available to anyone with Internet access. If you don't want people to know your e-mail address, for example, don't include it in any message you post publicly. PLEASE BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL WHEN DISCLOSING ANY INFORMATION IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE INFORMATION THAT YOU DISCLOSE IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. I. Third Party WebsiteThis statement applies solely to information collected on the Site. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, or who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads to you. Further, the Site may contain links to other websites.  Read the privacy policies of other websites carefully, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites.  J. Access to Your Information/ChoicesWe provide you with an opportunity to access your personal information to ensure it is correct, accurate and current. To edit your personally identifiable information, please contact us at: info@authenticbrandsgroup.com. If for any reason you are not able to update or edit your personally identifiable information at this page, you can access such information by contacting us as described below. We will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request.  K. AssignmentIn the event that all or part of our assets or sold or acquired by another party, or in the event of a merger, you grant us the right to assign the personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected via the Site. L. Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will also revise the "last update" date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on the Site.  M. SecurityNo data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you understand that any information that you transfer to us is done at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. The standard security measures we use will depend on the type of information collected.  We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.  We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.N. Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at legaldept@authenticbrandsgroup.com. All information you provide in any written communication will also be covered by this Privacy Policy. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTSBeginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding ours disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us: ABG Collective, LLCc/o Authentic Brands Group LLC1411 Broadway, 4th FloorNew York, NY 10018Last Updated On: April 1, 2016
I want to change the color of this area.
